<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">
<head>
<styling>
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="left" tts:fontSize="20 px"/>
</styling>
</head>
<body>
<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00:00:00.30" dur="7433 ms" style="1">An initial survey of the battlefield is crucial to planning tactics,&lt;br /&gt;so let's get familiar with the camera first. </p>
<p begin="00:00:07.73" dur="7633 ms" style="1">We can change our view of the battlefield by using&lt;br /&gt;the WASD keys, with the Q and E keys rotating our view.</p>
<p begin="00:00:15.36" dur="7633 ms" style="1">Scroll the mouse wheel and we can zoom in on our forces.&lt;br /&gt;Double clicking a unit or its unit card, centres and</p>
<p begin="00:00:22.99" dur="3200 ms" style="1">zooms the camera on its field of view. </p>
<p begin="00:00:26.83" dur="7911 ms" style="1">We're in the opening stage of a battle right now – the deployment phase.&lt;br /&gt;At this point, we can tweak the position of our army by moving</p>
<p begin="00:00:34.74" dur="8111 ms" style="1">our units to locations within the outlined deployment zone. This planning&lt;br /&gt;stage is a feature of every battle, unless we're surprised</p>
<p begin="00:00:42.85" dur="3900 ms" style="1">by an enemy ambush on the campaign map.</p>
<p begin="00:00:47.46" dur="8700 ms" style="1">We need to select a unit before we can change its position. &lt;br /&gt;We can either left-click on the unit itself, or on its unit card.</p>
<p begin="00:00:56.16" dur="7500 ms" style="1">Now we can instantly place it by right-clicking on a new location. &lt;br /&gt;Once the battle starts, we'll use this same method to issue move orders.</p>
<p begin="00:01:04.36" dur="9450 ms" style="1">Let's widen the line of this unit. With the unit selected, &lt;br /&gt;we hold down the right-mouse button and drag the mouse. </p>
<p begin="00:01:13.81" dur="7500 ms" style="1">We can also alter the depth of a unit and its facing in the same way. &lt;br /&gt;The manoeuvre compass allows us to fine tune unit positioning that little bit more.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
