<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">
<head>
<styling>
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="left" tts:fontSize="20 px"/>
</styling>
</head>
<body>
<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00:00:00.30" dur="6416 ms" style="1">We can continue fighting battles, conquering provinces and&lt;br /&gt;progressing our avatar but let's take things further by playing the </p>
<p begin="00:00:06.71" dur="3200 ms" style="1">clan competition.</p>
<p begin="00:00:10.53" dur="6816 ms" style="1">To join a clan we first need to be a member of a Steam Group.&lt;br /&gt;The Clan Page lists all the public Steam Groups open to us and those </p>
<p begin="00:00:17.34" dur="6700 ms" style="1">we've already joined. We simply choose one of our Groups and&lt;br /&gt;label this as our clan. </p>
<p begin="00:00:25.36" dur="7022 ms" style="1">Clans compete in worlds with 23 others, fighting over possession&lt;br /&gt;of provinces on the Avatar Conquest map. Clans are ranked </p>
<p begin="00:00:32.38" dur="7222 ms" style="1">according to the number of provinces they control. Owned provinces&lt;br /&gt;are displayed via colour coding on the map. We can view </p>
<p begin="00:00:39.61" dur="4800 ms" style="1">more details on this province via the tooltips.</p>
<p begin="00:00:45.03" dur="7466 ms" style="1">Provinces are won by earning Clan Influence. This influence is&lt;br /&gt;increased as clan members earn victories in a province. The control </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.49" dur="2400 ms" style="1">of surrounding provinces also contributes influence.</p>
<p begin="00:00:55.56" dur="7516 ms" style="1">The clan leader can mark a province as a priority target for their&lt;br /&gt;members. By winning battles for our clan, we can earn tokens.</p>
<p begin="00:01:02.98" dur="7000 ms" style="1">These clan tokens can be used to upgrade our veteran units&lt;br /&gt;with new abilities and to reset our avatar skills.</p>
<p begin="00:01:10.60" dur="7716 ms" style="1">Worlds are arranged in a pyramid system. At the end of a season,&lt;br /&gt;normally a two-week period, the top clans are promoted up the </p>
<p begin="00:01:18.31" dur="6000 ms" style="1">pyramid. The bottom clans are also relegated down a level before&lt;br /&gt;the next season begins.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
