<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">
<head>
<styling>
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="left" tts:fontSize="20 px"/>
</styling>
</head>
<body>
<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00:00:00.30" dur="7688 ms" style="1">Enough posturing, it's time to engage! The enemy have a unit of Yari Kachi&lt;br /&gt;split away from their main army - let's pick them off.</p>
<p begin="00:00:07.98" dur="7888 ms" style="1">We'll send in our Katana Kachi to face them, their swords&lt;br /&gt;and superior melee skills should overwhelm the enemy.</p>
<p begin="00:00:15.87" dur="5200 ms" style="1">We'll select our unit and right-click on our target to order the attack.</p>
<p begin="00:00:21.76" dur="7083 ms" style="1">If we charge an enemy at speed, our attack will be more devastating.&lt;br /&gt;That's particularly true when attacking with cavalry units.</p>
<p begin="00:00:28.85" dur="6400 ms" style="1">Let's round up our Yari Ki cavalry and look to smash the enemy line. </p>
<p begin="00:00:35.93" dur="8483 ms" style="1">By double right-clicking on an enemy, we'll order our cavalry to charge&lt;br /&gt;and the impact will inflict more damage. Charging spear units</p>
<p begin="00:00:44.41" dur="9400 ms" style="1">with cavalry is never a good idea, but if we attack the enemy's flank or rear,&lt;br /&gt;it will be far more effective than engaging them head-on.</p>
<p begin="00:00:54.50" dur="6800 ms" style="1">Our cavalry charge was devastating! The white bar above&lt;br /&gt;the enemy banner indicates that the unit has routed.</p>
<p begin="00:01:01.30" dur="7000 ms" style="1">This occurs when the morale of a unit is broken. &lt;br /&gt;Heavy casualties, exposure to an enemy on the flank or rear,</p>
<p begin="00:01:08.30" dur="6500 ms" style="1">or the untimely death of their General, can all damage a unit's morale.</p>
<p begin="00:01:15.43" dur="8583 ms" style="1">Morale can be maintained in a number of ways. Proximity to friendly&lt;br /&gt;units is important, while a nearby General can also be a major factor.</p>
<p begin="00:01:24.01" dur="8500 ms" style="1">A General has a number of special abilities that can quickly boost &lt;br /&gt;the morale of a unit, even when the odds are stacked against them.</p>
<p begin="00:01:33.20" dur="8933 ms" style="1">Other units also have special abilities – their controls are always&lt;br /&gt;located near the manoeuvre compass. Some abilities can only be used sparingly; </p>
<p begin="00:01:42.13" dur="6800 ms" style="1">they have &quot;cooldown&quot; times which will limit how often you can&lt;br /&gt;bring them into play.</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
