<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<tt xml:lang="en" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1" xmlns:tts="http://www.w3.org/2006/04/ttaf1#styling">
<head>
<styling>
<style id="1" tts:textAlign="left" tts:fontSize="20 px"/>
</styling>
</head>
<body>
<div xml:lang="en">
<p begin="00:00:00.30" dur="8233 ms" style="1">We've engaged the enemy hand-to-hand, but we also have a variety of&lt;br /&gt;western-inspired firepower at our disposal, capable of cutting down an</p>
<p begin="00:00:08.53" dur="7100 ms" style="1">enemy from range. Let's select our Line Infantry and start to use some of&lt;br /&gt;that firepower now.</p>
<p begin="00:00:16.26" dur="6866 ms" style="1">Our Line Infantry carry rifles. They are a direct fire unit that need&lt;br /&gt;a clear line of sight on their enemy to be effective. </p>
<p begin="00:00:23.13" dur="7566 ms" style="1">While bowmen can fire over obstacles, rifle units need to be positioned &lt;br /&gt;carefully to give them a clear field of fire. That arc drawn </p>
<p begin="00:00:30.69" dur="4000 ms" style="1">in front of our unit shows their firing range.</p>
<p begin="00:00:35.36" dur="8055 ms" style="1">Artillery units offer us even more firepower.Our guns can be&lt;br /&gt;attached or &quot;limbered&quot; to horses and pulled around the battlefield. </p>
<p begin="00:00:43.92" dur="8255 ms" style="1">Once unlimbered, they can  be used to inflict heavy casualties on &lt;br /&gt;approaching enemies. They're also very handy when it comes to </p>
<p begin="00:00:52.67" dur="6100 ms" style="1">destroying wall defences in sieges.</p>
<p begin="00:00:59.20" dur="6522 ms" style="1">These Gatling guns are our most fearsome artillery weapon. &lt;br /&gt;Let's use them on the advancing enemy! </p>
<p begin="00:01:05.72" dur="6722 ms" style="1">With the unit selected, we can choose to either target enemy troops directly,&lt;br /&gt;or focus fire on any area of the battlefield, </p>
<p begin="00:01:12.44" dur="9400 ms" style="1">creating a kill zone that will help block a would-be advance. &lt;br /&gt;Either way, any unit who ventures within range will be quickly shot to pieces!</p>
</div>
</body>
</tt>
